Hello?
I miss you more
Do you have a schedule
for tomorrow?
No, I don't
I'll pick you up
at your place then
Okay
I gotta go now
Talk to you later
Okay
This is the place
Is it?
Gosh, it's been a while
It's not crowded
on weekdays, I guess
Did you come here often?
Yeah, a few times
Our practice room
was around here
You wanna try that?
That one?
Yeah, I'm good at that
Are you afraid
you can't beat me?
Let's do it
Hyesung
Were you good
at PE in school?
Yeah, I was quite good
How about you?
I was also good
I think I worked hard
until middle school
It might be a shame that
you were too busy
to enjoy a school life
Well… not really
I rather wanted
to make money first
What for?
My grandma was sick
You were quite close
to your grandma, I guess
Yes
Since she passed away
I've been always lonely
What about now?
Are you still lonely?